Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Did something happen?
What's wrong?
What is it?
Can you...
take me and run away somewhere?
It's okay if I can't be forgiven.
No, I won't accept any forgiveness.
So...let's run away.
Run away with me.
Let's run away!
Episode 12
If the Earth were square, I'd really try running away.
Why does it have to be round?
This sucks.
No matter where you run, you'll end up back home.
Don't say anything like that again.
Let's run away?
Sure, let's go.
Let's run away.
Let's run to the end of the world and hide somewhere no one knows.
What would you do if I had said that?
Would you really go with me
if I agreed?
If you're suffering so much, what can I do?
You just stay still.
Do only what you want to do. If you want to bow down to
Hyo Seon's toenails, go ahead and do it.
If you don't want to do that, then force her to the wall as you did before,
blame her and pressure her.
Do that.
Just do what you want to do. I'll take care of everything else.
I...
I know what my heart is thinking very well,
but why are you like this?
What did you do wrong
for you to do so much for this family?
Is there something you have your eyes on?
Just like my mother?
There's something I need to repent for.
If I don't, I feel like I'll be like Dracula, not being able to die no matter how hard I try,
and having to live for thousands of years.
What did you do?
I...
can't tell you.
What if...
I run away by myself?
If that's what you want to do, then do it.
If you want to run away by yourself,
I'll do all I can to help you.
Where do you want to go?
No. Don't ask me to stay.
Things would've been better if you had just let me leave.
Things would not have turned out this way.
Please forgive me.
No matter what I do, you'll forgive me anyway.
I'm tired of apologizing now.
I'll take you where you want to go. Get in.
I knew this would happen.
You're here.
I didn't know how much we have to make, so I was going to ask you.
We've made the same amount as we usually did.
We didn't want to wake you just to ask you.
Little President has come out? You came out early.
What's wrong? Does that sound weird?
We need a title to call you by,
but since you're so young, calling you "president" seems a bit weird.
Little President, are you done preparing for the prayer ritual?
The taste of the yeast will change depending on how the ritual is carried out.
We'll only trust in you, Little President.
It's great weather for making yeast today, isn't it?
- Do you think so?
- It's so beautiful today.
- Of course.
- I have a feeling the best yeast will be prepared today!
Of course!
Let's get a move on.
Step on it harder!
I'm already stepping on it hard!
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear, ah  ♫
♫ I can't bear it, so I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again  ♫
Why aren't you wearing any gloves?
Eat something, kiddo. Why are you working so hard?
Enjoy your food.
The business at Noona's winery is so slow that at least I should work really hard, Ahjussi.
If things go just a bit wrong, my Noona Eun Jo will go hungry.
Hello.
Have a seat.
Why did you ask to meet me?
Do you remember me?
No, how would I remember?
You said you work for Hyo Seon's family.
I guess you're more than that. What do you want from me?
There is a good topic for in-depth reporting. I wanted to tell you.
So what if you write the article?
Since the piece you wrote and submitted didn't draw enough attention.
You said it didn't draw enough attention?
Yes. You know, business newspapers do not have wide circulation.
- That's not the case for online.
- Online?
There is some reaction. Not so much because of Dae Seong True Winemakers,
but people remembering the "Trash Dumpling Scandal" first started to show some response.
So people's attention is directed more to the Trash Dumpling Scandal than to Dae Seong True Winemakers.
So my company is also planning a series on reviewing the Trash Dumpling Scandal.
Right. That's a good thing too, Dong Soo.
Can't you look into writing about Dae Seong True Winemakers too?
Since your father works at Dae Seong True Winemakers.
- I have something I'm curious about.
- Go ahead and ask me.
Has it been revealed who created the adulterated supply of rice wine?
Yes. He's been sentenced to probation and received a penalty fine.
Blue Lord of the East...
Red Lord of the South...
White Lord of the West...
Black Lord of the North...
May 6 in the year of the Black Horse (2002), I invoke the guardian gods of the five directions and five earths.
I, owner of Gu Dae Seong True Winemaker, Goo Eun Jo
respectfully ask the territorial gods (5 direction gods)
that I shall be making several hundreds, thousands of batches of leavening.
The path is pressed vertically and horizontally forming a border
and each of the five gods is arranged on the periphery.
We bow as we offer up this wine.
May you bestow divine blessings and oversee all our wishes.
21s Current affairs
Trainee Reporter Kim Dong So
I'm a trainee reporter here.
I saw that you contributed a piece to another magazine and not ours.
Your submission seems to have raised some interest.
Dong Soo's Chief Editor asked him to cover your story separately.
Shall we start the interview?
Where do you want to do it? Should we do it here?
Sure. Hold on, let me call over the photographer.
You really thought Hyo Seon's dad didn't know?
He knew everything.
Even though he knew, he still loved you, Mom.
You wouldn't be able to complain even if you were dropped into hell.
He loved you. Hyo Seon's dad did.
Mom. The sacrificial rice cakes, offered to the spirits at the ritual, are supposed to be shared and eaten by everyone.
Mom, you also must eat some of it.
Let's eat it together, Mom..
Just like Hyo Seon's dad, she also said that it's fine with her if you don't like her.
Because she likes you, she said nothing else bothers her.
Mom. Where you can find a father like that?
Where you can find a daughter like that, Mom?
Where else in the world can you find people like them?!
They're delicious. The rice cakes turned out especially delicious this time.
Since we must share and eat them with everyone without making any exceptions.
Let's eat them while they're warm, Mom. I didn't eat any yet either.
I told you to stop pestering me.
Mom. They're not just regular rice cakes, they're sacrificial rice cakes offered to the spirits at the ritual.
We're supposed to share and eat them with everyone who have good wishes for the company.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you making fun of me? Do I seem that easy to you?
Didn't you understand me telling you to leave me alone?
Why do you keep being a brown noser? Who's going to take a liking to you here?
Mom, you shouldn't act that way with food.
Are you going to make rice? I'll do it..
Are you going to make soup?
Then you make the soup and I'll cook the rice.
Where's the rice?
You do it all then!
You do it all.
Make the rice, make the soup and get the vegetables seasoned too.
Okay, Mom.
I can't guarantee the taste, but I'll cook everything.
Then, you go in and get some sleep.
And... You must eat some rice cakes.
You understand, right?
She is such a sly fox.
She's been acting all innocent at first, but turns out to be such a large vixen..
And so, the vegetables have been completely over-boiled.
How are you supposed to boil vegetables?
You know that I boil them really well, for as long as I could.
You're supposed to blanch vegetables slightly, not boil them completely.
What's the difference between blanching and boiling?
This won't do. I'll go ahead and do it.
No, Grandma. I'll do it.
You've never tried cooking anything before, not even ramyon of all things possible.
How do you think you're going to make seasoned vegetables? They're seasoned vegetables after all!
Excuse me. There are still some seasoned vegetables left after the ritual.
Can't she just take some and eat them for now?
There are seasoned vegetables? There are some left, Ahjumma?
Ahjumma, thank you. Grandmother, thank you.
Hyo Seon is back.
Mom..
What are those?
The vegetables from earlier turned into a grass mix,
I went to go ask Grandma how to cook them,
but Ahjumma said that there were some left from the ritual.
Grandma? Ahjumma?
I'm definitely sure I sent them away.
So, what Grandma and Ahjumma are you talking about?
There aren't many people left working in the winery...
So, Eun Jo...
No, Unni...
I asked you to season the namool (boiled vegetable) but you didn't want to do it.
So you were going to put that on the table and say that you made it?
No, Mom. That's not it.
And you bring back the people that I sent out?
That's not it! I didn't-
And, you used Eun Jo as an excuse for it!
No, Mom.
It's not as an excuse...
You... Shut up.
Don't even say a word because I feel like fainting
just at the sound of your voice.
Mom.
Mom! Mom!
Mom...
Let go of me! Where are they hiding?
Do you clearly deceive a person like this??
Is it okay to trick someone like this?
What on earth did you think I meant when I told you to get out of here?
When someone tells you to get out of their house, don't you know what that means?!
Mom. Back then, all the ahjussies stopped working and quit.
The winery was really in desperate need of workers.
Did she ask you to come back? Did she say she couldn't live here because her step-mother was so horrible,
that she needed the Granny and Auntie who raised her like their own?
Did she hold on to you?
This is a big deal. You've got a lot of misunderstandings,
that's making a big deal out of this situation.
Madam, please ask Big Miss.
Because Big Miss asked us to stay here...
Oh, Grandma! The people who work are so hungry!
Why aren't you feeding us when it's already past lunch time...?
You still haven't left Hyo Seon's Uncle?
The thing is that...
Mom, please.
If Uncle is kicked out of here, he really has nowhere else to go, Mom.
Look here, Hyo Seon's Uncle.
You can't do this. Who's fault is it that this household is in this mess?
Whose fault is it that our Joon Soo's dad left like that so abruptly?!
How? With what nerve? With what conscience?
Are you coming into and leaving my house!
Mom..
Hey talk to me if you have a mouth! Are you an idiot?!
You still don't know what make your dad be gone?
If only your Uncle hadn't caused all this trouble-
Mom!
Let go of me, you brat! Why do I have
to be dragged into my own house, you brat?!
Let go of me.
Why are you looking at me with such brazen eyes, looking to talk haughtily to me?!
Did I say something wrong?
Who are you to call back all the people I chased out?
Mom... Mom, you're on my side, right?
- You're not on Hyo Seon's side, right?
- What?
If we add your share, mine and Jun Soo's together,
it will be three and a half times as much as Hyo Seon's?
Does Hyo Seon have to get that much?
Hyo Seon ... she's just an idiot,
if you act all nice to her, we can get it all.
She's an idiot. She says that she'd rather have a nagging mom like you
than not have a mom at all.
Do you think I'm telling you to be kind to her because I can't handle an idiot like her?
What you're doing to Hyo Seon,
chasing out her Uncle and the kitchen staff.
All the workers and elders of the house found out about that.
Once the elders of the household start talking,
everything that you and I can take shrinks.
What kind of bullshit is that?
What do the elders have to do with this household?
Dae Seong True Wine Makers is no longer ours, Mom.
Since we couldn't pay back the money the elders loaned us,
we gave the elders shares to Dae Seong True Winemakers.
When?!
Do you think that's all?
When you go against Hyo Seon and the workers,
all the elders who have shares will take Hyo Seon's side.
It's a matter of time before our shares hit rock bottom.
The ancestral mountain and 200000 plots of farmland...
All that, too, is jointly owned by those people.
Don't you think we need to get that too?
If we want to sell the land, but Hyo Seon disagrees, then we can't sell it.
Really?
Stop being mean to Hyo Seon.
Since you're acting this way, it makes me want to treat Hyo Seon super well.
But like you said, I can't put on that kind of act.
That's why you need to treat her well in my place, okay?
Do you not understand what I'm saying?
I'm saying there's a lot you can take from Hyo Seon.
Noona.
Let's go to the hospital. We have to get you examined first,
It's not that sort of thing.
It's just that my heart got a little stuffy..
She told me not to cry.
Eun Jo did.
She must not like it when people cry.
It's okay.
Still... I'm not clinging on anymore.
There are times when she's friendly.
But still...
I feel so overwhelmed, Oppa.
Why do you think I was born like this, Oppa?
I miss Dad so much, Oppa..
I miss him so much that I could die.
You can't cry because Eun Jo told you not to cry?
Cry. You feel overwhelmed because you can't cry.
Cry. You're in front of me now.
Can I do that?
Yes.
You can cry aloud.
I'm sorry ... sorry,
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Hyo Seon.
Nurungji Makgeolli, 1,500 won.
Place of Production, Nurungji Winery..
You're not going to ask me how I've been doing while I was away?
You said you were going to the reserve forces training. I'm sure you've been well.
Bok Boon Da Makgeolli, 1,800 won.
Place of Production, Dong Shin. Type is aged makgeolli.
You're still wearing the bread (brooch), right?
Bread. I'm asking if you still wear the bread!
Soo Da Makgeolli, 1,700 won.
Place of Production, Soo Da Makgeolli.
Jo Won Soo Makgeolli, 1,800 won.
If you need any help, let me know.
How much money could you possibly have that you always offer me some?
It's yours.
What's this?
I won it playing "Go Stop".
What?
It's nothing. I was just kidding.
You..aren't you going to eat?
Your face looks so thin and pale. Get up immediately.
What are you doing?! I have a mountain load of work to do!!
I'm just telling you to eat while you work!
Do you want to fool around? I told you to not fool around!!
- You shouldn't fool around either.
- What?
I don't know about anything else, but I won't let you not eat.
Follow me.
Come on.
Welcome.
Unni.
What kind of relationship do you two have?
What relationship?
"Song Eun Jo is Han Jeong Woo's woman forever." What was that bat about?
Ah, that's...
If you finished eating your meal, let's go.
No. Why aren't you finishing your rice? It's rice after all.
You and I... we can't leave any leftovers.
Hyo Seon, eat.
Eat lots. Why are you so thin?
Hyo Seon is back.
You're back, Hyo Seon?
Did you eat dinner already?
We did.
Ah, is that so? Then, you should wash up and go to bed.
Just go to sleep.
I should say "hi" to Mom.
You already did. Just sleep.
Are you this happy because Mom isn't getting angry at you?
Is it obvious?
It makes me a little nervous...
It makes me a little nervous.
But, I'm happy.
This is the only one that's just right.
What did you say?
The rest of the drinks taste different.
How is it different? We made them all the same!
It means the yeast made all different tastes.
It's okay. Anyway, we've still succeeded.
We can just research what needs to be come to make the yeast all taste the same.
The makgeolli made of nature. Dae Seong True Winemakers Makgeolli.
The makgeolli made of nature. Dae Seong True Wineakers Makgeolli.
Miss Mi Yoo Ra has rescinded the contract.
To be precise, she refuses to stamp the contract.
What are you talking about?
She said there's a problem with the quality of the makgeolli.
What problem?
Instead of saying that there's a problem with Hong Joo Ga's makgeolli,
she says that she's decided to go for a better quality product.
A better quality product?
Last time, Dae Seong True Wineamakers ...
Half of what was in the container was unloaded and marketed in Japan.
- The reception...
- What about the reception?
was great.
Great?
Amongst the youngsters in Japan, it's a trend to search up information
about Dae Sung True Winemakers before their friends.
They say the commercial video for Dae Seong True Winemakers,
as well as their advertisement pages
are circulating all over.
So much that it can be seen as a strange fandom phenomenon.
Didn't you report that the yeast was not completely successful?
The ingredient prepared by the late owner was all used up
and the 2nd generation is not capable enough to prepare it,
isn't that what you reported?
So, how is it possible that Dae Seong True Winemakers has been able to receive new orders?
Gi Hoon is said to have negotiated with Mr. Miura.
He asked to borrow the latest technology
and equipment to complete the unfinished yeast development.
Mr. Miura is positively reviewing the request.
Until that came to pass, what have you been doing?
What were you doing?!
Yes. Yes, thank you very much. (In Japanese)
We'll try to come to a decision quickly and let you know as soon as possible.
Let's do it.
Let's lease the machinery. Your yeast was not a failure.
All we need to do is figure out the conditions in which the yeast will produce the right taste.
Let's do it.
An opportunity like this is once in a lifetime.
Eun Jo, are you listening?
Eun Jo.
What if we fail again?
What if... we fall into debt again?
That won't happen.
Those people are businessmen to their core.
Would they offer us something like this without confidence that we would succeed?
Believe in yourself. I said believe in yourself.
This all happened
because I believed in myself.
At least you can ask Ajhusshi for forgiveness like this.
I don't have anything.
I'm jealous that you have a way.
He'll like it. Ahjussi will.
Don't do this.
This...
Please don't do it.
We have to give them an answer quickly.
You've made up your mind, right?
The costs are too high.
Even if we get orders, it'll basically be the same as giving out our first batch for free.
We'll have to take at least that much risk. You know that.
On top of that, we can't trust them.
What if we get tricked like last time?
This... isn't like that.
Why didn't I do anything?
Who did that...
Why they did that...
Why didn't I think of trying to find that out? Why did I stay still?
Eun Jo.
I'm going to find out. No matter what it takes, I'm going to catch them somehow.
What?
I'll do it.
I'll find out. It'll be better if I do it.
No, I'm going to do it.
I'll do it.
Eventually, I'll tell you why it is that I have to find out.
What do you mean?
Make the yeast samples quickly. Make a lot of them.
Prepare it so that we can export them to Japan as soon as possible.
If we succeed, ideally in 1-2 months, if it takes longer, at least within 6 months.
Dae Seong True Winemakers can rise again. If that happens,
Get in. I'll take you to the research lab.
"Dae Seong True Winemakers' Meaningful Movement"
"We Pride Ourselves on Making the Purest Makgeolli"
Please raise your face a little bit higher.
Okay, we're done. Finish it now...
But, why was I being photographed, Dong Soo?
On the back cover, we featured a reader reading our magazine.
You're the next issue's cover.
You can leave now. There's no reason for you to stay here.
If...
Last time's Japanese export incident...
Who did that, why they did it.
If we find out everything,
what are you going to do with those people?
I don't know.
I'll find the strength to live for something for the rest of my life.
I'm sure I'll overflow with energy
thinking of their faces and hating them with all my might.
I'll hate them without getting tired of hating them.
That'll be enough for me.
With the strength to hate them, I'll live well until I die.
You can go.
What?
What is it?
What are you doing right now?
My friend and I run a business together.
- It hasn't been long since we started.
- What?
Look around. When production begins,
You can supply us with Dae Seong True Winemakers makgeolli here.
- What?
- It'll be all right.
It hasn't been long since we opened it, but there are so many customers.
You aren't a reporter? I thought you were a reporter.
Haven't you heard of having two jobs?
Aren't you going to leave?
I'm done talking. Leave quickly.
What's wrong with me meeting that kid?
What is father trying to meet her for?
You don't need to know that.
What are you up to?
Stop interfering now.
I told you to leave this place as it is!
Do you have the right to say that?
Leave it?
Did you go into Dae Sung True Winemakers to leave it be?
If you meet with Eun Jo, what are you going to say?
I'd like to tell her a bit about what you did.
What did you say?
If I do that,
then I'll have to tell her what I did as well. But, I don't care.
Anyway, I'm going to lose everything.
Gi Jeong's mother is planning on filing for a divorce.
I'm supposed to hand over my shares as alimony.
If my shares go to Gi Jeong's mom...
In other words, that means they'll be Gi Jeong's.
Then, Hong Joo Ga will belong to Gi Jeong.
Since I'm about to lose everything anyway...
I came to confess all my sins.
Father.
What? Can't I do that?
Don't do this.
Don't do anything!
I heard you got some good news from Japan.
I heard that it was your doing.
If you don't want me to meet that child Eun Jo,
you better be on my side.
If you succeed, within 1-2 months at the earliest and within 6 months at the latest
Dae Sung True Winemakers can rise again.
Who are you?
Hand over Dae Seong True Winemakers which is appreciating in value.
Then, I will finish raising it.
That is the only way I can stay at Hong Distillery.
I refuse.
Then, I'll have no other choice. I'll have to meet that child named Eun Jo.
When will we be able to use the machine?
What?
You said to rent them. Let's do it.
Okay.
Let me do it as soon as possible. I can make at least a sample whenever we need.
Eun Jo.
Never mind. All right.
Are you coming back home now?
She told us to come back to the house all of a sudden. Madam did that.
I see. What about Ahjumma?
I came too.
Seriously telling us to believe that, right?
This is funny, isn't it?
Joon Soo, you should go to sleep now.
I don't want to.
Go to sleep immediately!
Aren't you going to sleep?
I just want to watch this.
- Ah, right. Mom.
- What?
Jang... Who was it?
Jang... Jang...
Do you know a man named Jang Taek Geun?
Who?
Do you or don't you?
I don't. Why?
You don't? Then forget it.
Earlier, while I was coming back home there was this kind of man that I saw...
What kind of man was that?
Mom, what is it?
It's funny.
What kind of man was that?
Oh, that kind of man asked if this is the house
where Jang Taek Geun's Noona, Song Kang Sook, lives.
So I told him that I know that my mom doesn't have any relatives
and that he got the wrong house.
You did well. I don't have any relatives.
Go on and sleep. I'm tired.
Okay. Sleep well.
All right, you sleep well too.
Mom, I know that you don't find me lovable.
But thank you for being kind to me regardless.
Later on, I really want you to give me a hug because you find me loveable.
I'll be good to you, Mom.
Who did it and why...
If we find out everything, what are you going to
do with those people?
I'll find the strength to live forever.
I'll overflow with strength thinking of their faces and hating them.
With the strength to despise those people, I'll live well until I die.
What?
Before you tell her, I'm going to confess first and end this.
If I tell her first, you'll be the only one who'll be ruined.
Unburdened, I can simply wait for her disposition.
I didn't know that was the best way of never letting you or hyung get your hands on Dae Seong True Winemakers.
Good night.
Father...
I'm going to Eun Jo now.
Father, you're done for.
Open the door. Open the door!
Open the door, Eun Jo.
Open the door. Eun Jo, open the door!
Eun Jo! Eun Jo!
Eun Jo!
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
♫  because, yes, you are the only one I love  ♫
♫  My bruised heart  ♫
♫  is shouting so that  ♫
♫  I can find you  ♫
♫  Wherever you are  ♫
♫  Can't you hear my voice?  ♫